findacode.com 2016-12-11

# Privacy Policy

#### Your Privacy

FindACode.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process business requests and services. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

#### What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When you register an account, we collect and store basic information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, your web site URLs, your IP address, and other information in order to set up and maintain your account and to help improve your user experience. 

#### How do we protect your information?

This site is hosted on a secured server that does not allow access to the public. Firewalls passwords, and encryption technology protect the information about our members which we collect and store.

#### What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not place any personally identifying information in the cookies on your computer or record any information about our visitors other than anonymous technical data used for statistical purposes only.

#### Will FindACode.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?

FindACode.com does not sell, trade, rent or publish your personal information to any third party. FindACode.com may provide anonymous aggregate statistics about our members, site traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

FindACode.com may release member information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our member agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of FindACode.com, our members, or others. 

#### In Summary

FindACode.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to assist and promote our members. We do not sell, trade, rent or publish any personal information.

#### Your Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by FindACode.com. If we make any changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

FindACode.com also provides links to external sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and FindACode.com has no control or influence over their policies other than the voluntary adherence to our suggested privacy policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. FindACode.com cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites or third-party advertisements, linked or otherwise.

As of: April 17, 2015  
Displayed: December 11, 2016

#### Questions and Feedback

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at info@FindACode.com .

Thank you for visiting FindACode.com!

## Our contact information:

> Find A Code, LLC  
>  62 East 300 North  
>  Spanish Fork, UT 84660  
>  Phone: 801-770-4203 (9-5 Mountain)  
>  Fax: 801-770-4428  
>  Email: [info@findacode.com](mailto:info@findacode.com)   
>
